{
    "subject": "resource/Dangerous_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Franchot_Tone",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Dangerous' stars Franchot Tone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8731187582015991,
            "question": "Is Franchot Tone known for his role in 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8471258878707886,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Franchot Tone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7389952540397644,
            "question": "What other films has Franchot Tone starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6981765031814575,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6016533374786377,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5418244004249573,
            "question": "Is Franchot Tone a well-known actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4769478738307953,
            "question": "Name an actor who appeared in the movie 'Dangerous'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.371391624212265,
            "question": "When was the film 'Dangerous' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3585211932659149,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Dangerous' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2592984735965729,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'Dangerous'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Dangerous' stars Franchot Tone.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4095_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Dangerous' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4095_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film 'Dangerous' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4095_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name an actor who appeared in the movie 'Dangerous'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4095_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4095_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context provided confirms that Bette Davis and Franchot Tone starred together in the film \"Dangerous,\" which is mentioned explicitly in one of the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}